<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Project Thin</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/log.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2015-01-15T19:00:00+13:00</updated><entry><title>Forth Day</title><link href="/forth-day.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-15T19:00:00+13:00</updated><author><name>Anonymous</name></author><id>tag:,2015-01-15:forth-day.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;12:45am: 1 slice of banana bread with butter and peanut butter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11am: 44g of Uncle Toby's Cheerios with a drop of milk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12pm: 1500m Swim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2pm: 5 pieces of sushi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8pm: 2 slices of pizza, small BBQ lamb piece and half a serving of pasta.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Third Day</title><link href="/third-day.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-14T19:00:00+13:00</updated><author><name>Anonymous</name></author><id>tag:,2015-01-14:third-day.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;9am: I had 51g of Uncle Toby's Cheerios and 184ml of milk. Also gave in to having some of the non-added-sugar banana cake (2 small pieces).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1pm: 1 cheese, ham and tomato sandwitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5pm: 2 small slices of sugar-free banana cake and some home made banana ice cream with berries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8pm: BBQ; 2 pieces of chicken, 1 sausage, 1 kebab (chicken), 2 servings of potato salad.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Second Day</title><link href="/second-day.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-13T19:00:00+13:00</updated><author><name>Anonymous</name></author><id>tag:,2015-01-13:second-day.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;1am: Gave in to a tea spoon of Really Good Peanut Butter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9am: I had 50g of Uncle Toby's Cheerios and a big cup of coffee with 4 cups and some Coffee Mate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1pm: Stir fried 1 brocoli, 3 carrots and 200g of whole grain rice with 2 eggs and some olive oil, spices, a tsp of peanut butter and soy sauce.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6pm: Same as at 1pm (left overs).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30pm: 2 apples with 1 tbsp of peanut butter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30pm: Half a slice of bread with cheese, tomato and a leaf of basil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:30pm: 2 slices of banana cake with 7 strawberries. Banana cake without added sugar.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>My First Day</title><link href="/my-first-day.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-12T23:52:00+13:00</updated><author><name>Anonymous</name></author><id>tag:,2015-01-12:my-first-day.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is to introduce what I'm doing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have committed to a New Year's Resolution that I will loose at least 10kg this year. I actually want this to be a reality, because, of course, being thin is great, you are better looking, you feel better and more confident and you don't have to carry around all that redundant weight, which is just a bother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To cut a long story short, I want to record here what I have eaten and done in exercise to know what I've done to get back into shape. Also, this might help vent the craving etc that I go through while minimising the amount of sugar and carbs intake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OK, day 1:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I've come back from a visit to my friends in a city a few hours away. We had a great time and for breakfast/brunch I had a protein based meal with avocado, salmon, 2 eggs, 2 mushrooms and some greens. I also had a flat white coffee and a mango smoothy, I guess one shouldn't start out too radically ;-).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, for dinner, I had a smallish portion of lasagne and a muffin, again some sugar, but for it being everything today, that's not too bad. I also had a beer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, I got hungry and craved for something sweet and had a banana and a few cherries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, over all, not a perfect day, but I did feel good for not over-eating.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>